Toni Morrison Papers, 1917-2015: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Writings, 1917-2015; 66 boxes
  - Subseries 1A: Novels, 1917-2015; 1970-2015; 66 boxes
    - Home, 1948-2012; 2008-2012; 6 boxes
      - Home Drafts, circa 2005-2011; 3 boxes (1 partial)
        - Money, circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 12)
        - Money/Justina Three, circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 13)
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 14)
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", circa 2005-2011; Printout. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 15)
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", July 29 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 16)
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", September 5 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 17)
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 18)
        - "Women are eager to talk to me...", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 19)
          Pages 28-29.
        - "porch, either in the hammock...", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 20)
          Pages 26-28.
        - "some more and when his lady came to help...", circa 2005-2011; Printout. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 21)
          Pages 20-32.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 22)
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 23)
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", circa 2005-2011; Printout. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 24)
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 25)
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 26)
          Pages 1-51.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", circa 2005-2011; Printout. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 27)
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", June 15 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 59, Folder 28)
          Pages 1-65.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", July 1 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 60, Folder 1)
          Pages 1-71.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 60, Folder 2)
          Pages 1-68.
        - "soaked future...", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 60, Folder 3)
          Pages 63-74.
        - "Women are eager to talk to me...", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 60, Folder 4)
          Pages 59-77.
        - "2. Breathing...", circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 60, Folder 5)
          Pages 5-97.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", January 22 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 60, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-96.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", March 20 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 60, Folder 7)
          Pages 1-105.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", May 16 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 60, Folder 8)
          Pages 1-120.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", May 29 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 60, Folder 9)
          Pages 1-128.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", June 1 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 60, Folder 10)
          Pages 1-137.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", June 13 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 61, Folder 1)
          Pages 1-149.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", July 3 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 61, Folder 2)
          Pages 1-172.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", July 7 no year; Printout. 1 item (Box 61, Folder 3)
          Pages 1-135.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", July 17 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 61, Folder 4)
          Pages 1-181.
        - Home Draft, as "Frank Money", circa 2005-2011; Printout. 1 item (Box 61, Folder 5)
          Pages 1-194.
        - Home Draft, circa 2005-2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 61, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-198.
      - Home Copyedited Manuscript, 2011 October 27; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 62, Folder 1)
        Pages i-vii, 1-119. With copyeditor and publisher memos, dated October 25 and 27, 2011
      - Home Copyedited Manuscript with Robert Gottlieb and Toni Morrison edits, 2011 November 14; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 62, Folder 2)
        Pages i-vii, 1-117.
      - Home Setting Copy, 2011; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 62, Folder 3)
        Pages i-vii, 1-[118].
      - Home Page Proofs, 2011 December 7; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 4)
        Pages [i-x], 1-[146].
      - Home Corrected Proof Pages, 2011 December 7; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Home Page Proofs, 2012 February 6; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 6)
        Pages a-b, i-viii, 1-150.
      - Home Page Proofs, 2012 February 6; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Home Laser Proofs Master Set, 2012 February 24; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 8)
        Pages a-b, i-viii, 1-150. With Knopf Production memo dated February 28, 2012, and cover page dated March 8, 2012.
      - Home Layout Samples, 2011; 1 folder (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Home Advance Copy, 2012; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 10)
        Pages [1]-[146].
      - Home Dust-jacket Sample, 2012; 1 item (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - God Help the Child, 1998-2015; 4 boxes
      Working titles Bride, Bride Anew, Goodness, and The Wrath of Children.
      - God Help the Child Research Files, 1998-2014; 3 folders
        - Make-Up, 2012; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 1)
        - Miscellaneous, 2012-2013; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 2)
        - Prison, 1998-2014; 1 folder (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Outlines and Notes, circa 2005-2014; Notepad pages and printout, corrected. 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - "Man: I met a woman...", circa 2005-2014; Notepad. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 2)
        Includes material relating to A Mercy and Home.
      - "Bride 1. Direction of her journey...", circa 2005-2014; Notepad. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - "Wrath of Children", circa 2005-2014; Notepad. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - "1. Queen", circa 2005-2014; Notepad. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - "Orchestration", circa 2005-2014; Notepad pages and printout, corrected. 1 folder (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - God Help the Child Drafts, 2011 July 29-2012 December 21; 3 boxes (2 partial)
        - God Help the Child Draft, as "Bride Anew", circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 7)
        - God Help the Child Draft, as "Bride", circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 8)
        - God Help the Child Draft, 2011 July 29; Printout. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 9)
          Page 1-40.
        - God Help the Child Chapter Two Draft, circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 10)
          Pages 57-66.
        - God Help the Child Draft, circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 11)
          Pages 1-70.
        - God Help the Child Draft, circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 12)
          Pages 1-81.
        - God Help the Child Draft, 2012 December 21; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 13)
        - God Help the Child Part One Draft, circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 14)
          Pages 1-63.
        - God Help the Child Part Two Draft, circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 15)
          Pages 78-86.
        - God Help the Child Part Two Draft, circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 16)
          Pages 78-96.
        - God Help the Child Draft, as "Goodness", December 23 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 17)
          Pages 1-78.
        - Sofia, December 23 no year; Printout. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 18)
          Insert.
        - God Help the Child Draft Insert, circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 19)
        - "Now, sleepless and waiting...", circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 20)
          Pages 60-86.
        - "Hey Girl What's Inside Your Wooly Head...", circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 21)
          Pages 98-103.
        - God Help the Child Chapter Three Draft, circa 2005-2014; Printout. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 22)
          Pages 98-99.
        - God Help the Child Draft, as "Bride Anew", May 18 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 64, Folder 23)
          Pages 1-136.
        - God Help the Child Draft, as "The Wrath of Children", June 14 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 65, Folder 1)
        - God Help the Child Draft, as "The Wrath of Children", June 26 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 65, Folder 2)
          Pages 1-179.
        - "Once Queen was admitted...", July 23 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 65, Folder 3)
          Pages 151-154.
        - "'Doubt it.' Booker placed a cup of coffee...", July 25 no year; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 65, Folder 4)
          Pages 171-188.
        - God Help the Child Draft, as "The Wrath of Children", circa 2005-2014; Printout. 1 item (Box 65, Folder 5)
        - God Help the Child Draft, as "The Wrath of Children", circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 65, Folder 6)
          Pages 1-208.
        - God Help the Child Draft, as "The Wrath of Children", circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 65, Folder 7)
          Pages 1-232.
        - God Help the Child Draft, as "The Wrath of Children", circa 2005-2014; Printout. 1 item (Box 66, Folder 1)
          Pages 1-233.
        - God Help the Child Bride Insert, circa 2005-2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 66, Folder 2)
          Inserts.
      - God Help the Child Setting Copy, circa 2014; Printout, corrected. 1 item (Box 66, Folder 3)
        Pages a-b, i-vii, 1-[136].
      - God Help the Child Page Proofs, 2014 November 4; 1 item (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - God Help the Child First Pass Master Page Proofs, 2014 November 4; 1 item (Box 66, Folder 5)
        Pages 1-198, corrected pages at beginning.
      - God Help the Child Second Pass Master Page Proofs, 2015 January 15; 1 item (Box 66, Folder 6)
        Pages 1-182.
      - God Help the Child Laser Proofs, 2015 February 11; 1 item (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - God Help the Child Page Layout Samples, circa 2015; 1 item (Box 66, Folder 8)
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1953-2015; 35 boxes
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Consists primarily of personal correspondence sent to Morrison's home. Professional correspondence found Morrison's office working files and fan mail are not yet available.
  - 70th Birthday Cards, 2001; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - 75th Birthday Guest Book, 2006; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - 80th Birthday Cards, 2011; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - A, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
  - Abinader, Elmaz, 1986-1990; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Achebe, Chinua, 1991-2005; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Adams, Eve, 2004-2007; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Adero, Malaika, 1996-2007; 1 folder (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Ahearn, Eileen, 1979-2008; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Al Abdullah, Queen Raina, 2004; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Allen, Danielle, 2002-2013; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Allende, Isabel, 1987-2001; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Al Muhammad, Princess Firyal, 2013; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Als, Hilton, 2000-2003; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Annan, Kofi and Nane, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Angelou, Maya, 1994-2013; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Appiah, Anthony, 1990; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Asaro, Sal, 1997-2009; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Atanasoff, Jeanne, 1988-2015; 2 folders (Box 68, Folder 11-12)
    Includes photographs.
  - Atlas, James, 2000-2001; 1 folder (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - B, 1985-2015; 3 folders (Box 69, Folder 1-3)
  - Bach, Jean, 1992; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Bailey, Donna, 1982-2009; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Baker, Houston and Charlotte, 1987-1992; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Baldwin, Emma Berdis Jones, 1977-1999; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Baldwin, James, 1976, 1986; 1 folder (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Bambara, Toni Cade, 1977-1995; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 1, Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Banfield, Bill, 2002; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Banks, Russell, 1990-2002; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Baraka, Amiri and Amina, 1981-2004; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Batton, Susan Sayre, 1990-1994; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Belafonte, Harry, 1990; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Bell, Derrick, 1990-1996; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Benham, Joan A., 1999-2001; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Berg, Joel, 1982-2013; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Bergman, Robert and Laurie McCannel, 1997-2010; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Bernstein, Robert L., 1988-2002; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Bertolino, James, 1983; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Bezos, Mackenzie Tuttle, 1990-2014; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Bhabha, Homi, 1994-2011; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Bonetti, Kay, 1986-1987; 1 folder (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Bourgois, Christian and Dominique, 1988-2000; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Bowen, William, 1987-1998; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Boyle, Kay, 1984-1987; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Bracey, Phyllis Woods, 1988-2003; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Includes a photograph.
  - Bradley, Bill, 1994-1996; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Breitwieser, Mitch, 1988-1991; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Brombert, Beth and Victor, 1989-2008; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Brony, Elizabeth, 1995-1997; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Brooks, Cynthia, 1999; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Brooks, Georgia, 1971-2011; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1993-1997; 1 folder (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Brooks, Lois Wofford, 1982-2006; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 1, Box 71, Folder 12-13)
  - Brown, Carlene, 1977-2012; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Bruckner, Carol, undated; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Bush, Barbara, 1989; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Busia, Abena, 1985-2011; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Byatt, A.S., 1994-2001; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - C, 1977-2015; 2 folders (Box 72, Folder 7-8)
  - Cammerzell, Frederick, 1988-2008; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Caro, Robert, 1993; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Carpenter, Lea, 2003-2013; 1 folder (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Carrasco, David, 1991-2013; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Carroll, Doris, 1980-1995; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Carter, Graydon, 2001-2011; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Carter, Rosalynn and Jimmy, 1980-2009; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Casebere, James, 2008-2012; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Cepeda, Patricia, 1998-2000; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Champ, Norman B., 1987-1992; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Cheatwood, Kiarri T-H., 1981-1989; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Cheever, Susan, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Cisneros, Sandra, 1998 January 20; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Clark, Ana Steele and John, 1986-2011; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Clark, Larry, 1986; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Clemons, Dolores, 1986-1988; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Clinton, Bill and Hillary, 1993-2006; 1 folder (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Clinton, Bill and Hillary--White House Invitations, 1993-2000; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Coetzee, J.M., 2004; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Cole, Johnetta B., 1995; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Conarroe, Joel, 2005; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Conner, Marc, 2001-2005; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Cook, Beverly and Charles, 1988-1993; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Cooper, Bill, Clarissa, Ashley and Courtney, 2003; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Cornell, Drucilla, 1993-2007; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Cosby, Bill and Camille, 1986-1997; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Couric, Katie, 2012; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Curasi, Anne, 2009-2012; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - D, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 74, Folder 12-13)
  - d'Amboise, Jacques, 1987-2012; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Daniel, Clifton, 1983; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Danielpour, Richard, 2002-2007; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Danticat, Edwidge, 2014; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Eisa, 2005-2011; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Davis, Natalie Zemon, 1992-2013; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Davis, Thadious, 1998; 1 folder (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - Dee, Ruby and Ossie Davis, 1992-2012; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Dees, Morris, 2004; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - DeCrow, Karen, 1988-2006; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Demme, Jonathan, 1997-1999; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Denard, Carolyn, 1991-2015; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - DiFilippo, Rosemary, 1991-2014; 2 folders (Box 75, Folder 6-7)
  - Dimock, Peter, 1985-2010; 1 folder (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Dimock, Wai-Chee, 1985-1994; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Dinkins, David and Joyce, 1989-2007; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Dixon, Melvin, 1977-1987; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Doctorow, E.L., 2001; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Dorfman, Ariel, 1986-2002; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Dorris, Michael and Louise Erdrich, 1985-1993; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Dubois, Laurent, 1992-2005; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - E, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Elias, Robert and Helen, 1953-2013; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Ellison, Ralph and Fanny, undated; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - English, Lady Judith, 2005; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Epstein, Barbara, 2000; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Epstein, Jason, 1998-2003; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - F, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 76, Folder 14-15)
  - Fabre, Geneviève, 1992-2007; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Fagles, Robert and Lynne, 1994-2008; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Farrow, Mia, 1995-1997; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Faust, Drew, 2001; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Featherston, Natalie, 2004-2010; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Ferris, William, 1997-2009; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Fishkin, Shelley Fisher, 1992-2000; 1 folder (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Florio, Jim, 1993; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Forbes, Sheila, undated; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Forrest, Leon and Anne, 1998; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Foster, Jodie, 1985-1993; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Frankenthaler, Helen, 1986-1992; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Freedgood, Anne, 1980-1994; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Freedgood, Julia, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Frelinghuysen, Barrett, 2000-2013; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Freund, Gerald, 1987-1988; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Fulmer, Jackie, 1997-2003; 1 folder (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Fultz, Lucille, 1989-2015; 2 folders (Box 77, Folder 11-12)
  - G, 1970-2005; 2 folders (Box 77, Folder 13-14)
  - Gaines, Kevin, 1994; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Gass, William, 1985-1993; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Gates, Henry Louis, 1983-2008; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Gerzina, Gretchen Holbrook, 1986-2007; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Giddings, Paula, 1974-2009; 2 folders (Box 78, Folder 5-6)
  - Gilbert, Sandra, 1989-2005; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Ginsburg, Rachel and Philip, 1989-2012; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Giovanni, Nikki, 1989-2014; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Glasser, Barbara, 1988-2010; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Goellner, Ellen, 1992-2015; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Goerner, Lee, circa 1987-1992; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Goheen, Margaret and Robert, 1988-2008; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Gordimer, Nadine, 1985-2002; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Gornick, Vivian, 1990; 1 folder (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Graham, Billy, 2000-2011; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Graham, Maryemma, 2005-2015; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Grant, Alice, 1984-2003; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Grauer, Rhoda, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Greaves, William, 1988-2005; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Gregorian, Vartan, 1987-2012; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Griffin, Farah Jasmine, 2003-2013; 2 folders (Box 79, Folder 7-8)
  - Grosvenor, Vertamae, 1979-1994; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Groth, Patricia, 1985-1995; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Gubar, Susan, 1993-1995; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Guénif-Souilamas, Nacira, 2007; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Gunn, Bill, 1984; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Gutmann, Amy, 2000-2012; 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - H, 1970-2015; 2 folders (Box 79, Folder 15-16)
  - Haba, Jim and Erica, 1998-2007; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Hale, Janet Campbell, 1984-1985; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Harper, Conrad and Marsha, 1987-2008; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Harper, Michael S., 1975-2003; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Haskell, Molly, 1987-1994; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Hayes, Jennifer and Graham, 1996-2011; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Heaney, Seamus, 1996-1998; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Heiskell, Andrew, 1986-1996; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Hendricks, Obery, 2002-2003; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Herrin, Judith, 1992-1995; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Hickey, Meghan, 1996-2004; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Higginbotham, Jr., A. Leon, 1978-1998; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Hinton, William, 1984-1999; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Hodsoll, Frank, 1984-1988; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Holbrook, Hal, 2014; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Holt, Rush, 2012; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - hooks, bell, 1997; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Hoppenthaler, John, 2000; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Houston, Pam, 2003-2006; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Howe, Florence, 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - I, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - J, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Jacobozzi, Vivian, 1990-1997; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Johnson, Beth and Franklin, 1993; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Jones, Bill T., 2002-2006; 1 folder (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Jones, Patricia Spears, 2004-2005; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Jones, Quincy, 1986-2006; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Jong, Erica, 1995-2012; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Jordan, June, 1974-2002; 2 folders (Box 81, Folder 4-5)
  - Joseph, Peter and Wendy, 1997-2006; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - K, 1970-2005; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Kadish, Rachel, 1991-2005; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Kaess, Lisa, circa 2008-2010; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Kebede, Alitash, 1984-1987; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Kenan, Randall, 1985-1992; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Kennedy, Adrienne, 1984-1992; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Kennedy, Randall, 1994-2003; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Kennedy, William, 1985-1994; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Killian, Karl, undated; 1 folder (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Kilroy, Tom and Dotty, 1993-1996; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Kilson, Martin, 1996; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - King, Marion, 1988-1995; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Kingston, M. Ray, 1994; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Kingston, Maxine Hong, 1984-1993; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Knopf, Helen, 1981-1990; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Krantz, Bertha, 1988-1992; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Krementz, Jill, 1994-1996; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Krislov, Marvin, 2009-2015; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Kwayana, Tchaiko, 1988-2010; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - L, 1970-2015; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Lacour, Claudia Brodsky, 1990-2015; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Ladd, Florence, 1989-2011; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Lambrinidis, Christiana, 2007-2014; 1 folder (Box 82, Folder 14)